https://www.english-at-home.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
It is www.english-at-home.com’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we collect or which you provide to us. This privacy policy explains what types of personal information we receive, collect or use when you use and visit this site and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. The GDPR The EU General Data Protection Regulations (May 25 2018) give you much greater protection over your privacy and personal information. Here’s what you need to know: www.english-at-home.com are the “data controller”. If you have any questions about this policy or about how we use your Personal Data, please contact us via our contact details at the end of this policy. Personal Data we collect via www.english-at-home.com We only collect Personal Data where you choose to sign up to receive free content, including tips to learn English, plus special offers on promotions. We do not share your email address with anyone else, and you can unsubscribe any time via the link in the email. Data we collect automatically When you sign up to receive emails from us, we automatically record your IP address and time-stamp as proof of your consent. We automatically collect certain information when you visit our website, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, and the domain name of your ISP (internet service provider), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited. We do not link this information with any personal data. We may also collect data automatically through our use of cookies on the website. Google, as a third party vendor, uses advertising cookies to serve ads based on your previous visits to our website or other websites. You can opt out of personalised advertising by visiting Ads Settings Use of your Personal Data We will only use your Personal Data when the law allows us to. Sharing your Personal Data We take your privacy seriously and will not share your Personal Data with others, except as permitted by applicable law or as set out below: We share Personal Data as necessary with third parties located outside the EU who provide services to us and who require the information to provide those services. These third parties may include social media advertising platforms or email service providers. Please note that we have appropriate data privacy safeguards in place with these third parties. Keeping your Personal Data secure We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law, including the GDPR, to safeguard Personal Data from accidental loss, destruction or damage and unauthorised access, use and disclosure. Retention periods for use of your Personal Data We will use and store your Personal Data only for as long as necessary. We review the Personal Data we hold at regular intervals and delete permanently or anonymise any Personal Data which is no longer necessary. Children This website and our services are aimed at adults, and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Data relating to children aged under 15 years old. If you are under the age of 15, please do not provide us with any of your Personal Data, including your email address. Access to and control over your Personal Data You have legal rights under applicable law in relation to your Personal Data. You can ask the following questions, or take the following actions, at any time by contacting us via email ( support @ english-at-home.com)  or via our postal address: • see what Personal Data we hold about you (if any), including why we are holding it and who it could be disclosed to; • ask us to change/correct your Personal Data; • ask us to delete your Personal Data; • object to the processing of your Personal Data; • ask us to restrict the processing of your Personal Data; • withdraw any consents you have given us to the processing of your Personal Data; and • express any concerns you have about third parties’ use of your Personal Data. Change of purpose We will only use your Personal Data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to have an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us. If we need to use your Personal Data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so. Contact Us Our full details are: english-at-home.com LTD Email for Privacy Questions: support @ english-at-home.com Postal Address: 5, The Chambers Vineyard Abingdon-on-Thames OXON OX14 3PX   Speak English Fluently! Hi! I’m Clare, an English teacher and the founder of this site. I can help you speak English more easily! Here are two things for you: 10 Essential Fluency Phrases – Get the phrases for easy conversations NEW: Get An Advanced English Vocabulary In 30 Days – Go from Intermediate to Advanced level
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Get an Advanced English Vocabulary! – Get to advanced level in 30 days, in just 20 minutes a day – 30-Day Study Plan gives you exact steps – 5 proven memorisation strategies – 5 vocabulary-building techniques + Special bonus: 3 months vocabulary upgrades + free workshop Join the Advanced Vocabulary In 30 Days NOW   ×
